As you might imagine, a lot goes into designing
正如你想象的 很多人在设计
a robot even if it's a virtual robot rather than a real one.
机器人即使是虚拟机器人而不是真正的机器人
To make it possible for us to use turtle robots in Python,
为了让我们可以在 Python中使用海龟机器人
somebody had to write a bunch of code about turtles,
总得有人写一些关于海龟的代码
and here it is.
就在这里
This code makes it possible for us to create
这个代码让我们创造了
a turtle object and use simple instructions to have it draw things on the screen.
一个海龟对象 用简单的指令把它画在屏幕上
Now, that's a lot of code.
这就是很多代码
This is actually something you'll see a lot of in programming.
这其实是你在编程中看到的很多东西
Someone will write some useful code in a file and then share that file
某人将在文件中写入一些有用的代码 然后共享该文件
so everyone can use it and not have to write that same code over again themselves.
所以每个人都可以用它不用再写同样的代码
In Python, these collections of useful code are called modules.
在 Python 中 这些有用代码的集合称为模块
In this case, we've made use of the turtle module.
在这种情况下 我们利用了海龟模块
There are all kinds of other useful modules out there as well,
还有其他有用的模块
such as the math module,
比如数学模块
which has a bunch of code to help you do useful calculations.
它有一堆代码来帮助您进行有用的计算
You know, there are a lot of modules out there,
你知道那边有很多模块
and if we put all of those files of code into every program we write,
如果我们把所有这些文件都写进我们写的每一个节目
it would slow those programs down a lot.
会让那些节目变慢很多
So instead we tell Python when there's
所以我们要告诉 Python
a specific module that we want to use in our program.
我们计划中使用的特定模块
We do that by importing the module.
我们通过导入模块来完成此工作
That's what this first line of code import turtle is all about.
这就是第一行的密码输入性海龟
That's how we tell Python that we want to do things with turtles in
这就是我们如何告诉 Python 我们想用海龟做的事情
this program and we will therefore need access to the code that's in the turtle module.
因此 我们需要使用龟模块中的代码
Once we've imported the turtle module,
一旦我们输入了海龟模块
it's as if all the code we're a part of
就像我们所做的
our own program and we can access it to do things with turtles.
我们自己的节目 可以用海龟做事情
For example, let's take another look at this line, Amy equals turtle.Turtle.
例如 让我们再看看这一行  Amy 等于 turtle.Turtle
Remember, turtle.Turtle is the code that
记住龟龟
creates a new turtle object in the computer's memory.
在计算机内存中创建新的海龟对象
Notice how it starts with the name of the module that we need to use,
请注意 它以我们需要使用的模块的名称开始
turtle, and then there's a dot.
乌龟然后有个点
This dot is telling Python to look inside
这个点在告诉 Python
the turtle module for some code that is called turtle and run that code.
一个被称为海龟的代码的龟模块运行代码
So it saying run the turtle code that is inside the turtle module,
所以说运行乌龟模块里的乌龟代码
and it's that code that creates the new turtle object.
这就是创造新的海龟对象的代码
Now once the turtle object has been created,
一旦海龟被创造了
we can give that turtle instructions such as amy.forward100 or amy.right90.
我们可以给出 amy.forward100 或者 amy.right90之类的海龟指令
An important thing to understand about these lines is that they're
了解这些线的一个重要的事情是
actually referencing code that is hidden away somewhere else.
实际上引用隐藏在别处的代码
Specifically, these lines are referring to code that is inside that turtle module.
具体来说 这些线指的是龟模块内部的代码
In that module, there's a block of code that
在那个模块里有一个代码块
has instructions for getting the turtle to go forward,
有让乌龟前进的指示
and there's another block of code that has the instructions for getting it to turn right.
还有另一个代码块有指令让它右转
So, we have these blocks of code that have instructions for making the turtle
所以 我们有这些代码块 有让乌龟的指令
do different things but these blocks of code don't do anything by themselves,
做不同的事情但这些代码本身就不做任何事情
they just sit there waiting to be used.
他们就坐在那里等着被使用
When we run a line of code like amy.forward100,
当我们运行 amy.forward100这样的代码时
we are telling Python to find this block of code
我们告诉 Python 找到这个代码块
that has the name forward and run that code.
它具有该名称并运行该代码
In Python, these blocks of code are referred to as methods and we would refer to
在 Python 中 这些代码块称为方法 我们将引用
lines like amy.forward100 and amy.right90 as method calls.
amy.forward100 和 amy.right90 之类的行作为方法调用
When we run these lines,
当我们运行这些线路时
we are calling the forward and write methods that are in the turtle module.
我们正在调用海龟模块中的正向和写入方法
Amy.coloryellow is another example of a method call and it
Amy.color黄色是方法调用的另一个示例
is of course calling the block of code named color that is inside the turtle module.
当然是指乌龟模块内部的代号颜色的方块
Notice that these method calls always have the name of the method followed by
请注意 这些方法调用始终具有方法的名称 后跟
parentheses and we can put some input inside
我们可以在里面输入一些输入
the parentheses that Python will use when it runs the method.
Python 将在运行方法时使用的括号
So when we call the forward method,
所以当我们称之为前向方法时
it needs to know how much we want the turtle to move forward.
它需要知道我们希望乌龟前进的程度
So, here we're using the number 100 to tell it the number of pixels to move forward.
所以 这里我们用 100 号来告诉它要向前移动的像素数
When we call the write method,
当我们调用写作方法时
it needs input so that it knows how many degrees the turtle should turn.
它需要输入 让它知道乌龟应该转动多少度
And when we call the color method,
当我们用颜色的方法
it needs input like yellow or blue.
需要输入黄色或蓝色
If methods seem a little mysterious at this point,
如果这方面的方法有点神秘的话
don't worry, we'll come back to this concept again later on.
别担心我们稍后再回到这个概念
For now, it's enough to understand that we've got
现在已经足够理解了
a block of code that's hidden away somewhere else,
隐藏在别处的密码
that this code has a name and now we can run it by using lines
这个代码有个名字现在我们可以用线
like amy.forward100 or amy.right90.
如 amy.forward100 或 amy.right90